Let's now talk about Bootstrap's buttons.
现在让我们说说 Bootstrap 的按钮
In particular, the various classes that Bootstrap provides for
事实上 Bootstrap 提供了很多和按钮有关的类
you to include buttons in your website, and
从而你可以在你的网页中实现许多不同的按钮
also to style the buttons in various forms.
还可以在许多表格中运用不同风格的按钮
The default Bootstrap setup is configured with five different colors,
Bootstrap 按钮的默认设置中有 五种不同的颜色
and these colors can be specified within Bootstrap or
这些颜色可以通过
attached as qualifiers for previous classes in the form
设置不同的类来实现
of primary, success, info, warning and danger.
比如 primary 代表深蓝色 info 代表浅蓝色等等
There five corresponding colors in the default Bootstrap set up.
Bootstrap 里默认的类格式大部分为 xxx-yyy
Is darker blue for primary, green for success, light blue for info,
其中 xxx 是你的对象类别 比如说 text 或者 btn 或者 bg
an orange color, somewhat of an orange yellow color for
yyy 则是 primary, success, info, warning, danger 中的一个
warning, and red color for danger.
各自对应的颜色如图所示
These five colors, identifications,
这五种颜色
can be used together with many of the Bootstrap classes.
基本可以用在所有场合
So, for example, if we want to set a text to
举一些栗子 如果你想要天蓝色的 text
light blue in color they can say text info or you can say text primaries.
那么就设置 text-info
You can say button success for a green colored button, similarly,
如果你想要一个绿色的按钮 就设置 btn-success
alert danger for red colored and text to be displayed.
如果你想要一个红色的警告 就设置 alert-danger
Similarly, background info for
类似的 如果你想要一个天蓝色的背景
a blue colored background to be created for an element.
就在相应元素中设置 bg-info
So, this standard five color combinations
这五种颜色的组合
can be used together with many classes to specify colors for
可以用在几乎所有
those elements in Bootstrap.
你需要指定颜色的地方
Bootstrap provides various button classes that
我们之前说过 Bootstrap 提供了许多按钮的类
allow you to style your buttons in various ways.
它们允许你在不同场合使用不同风格的按钮
Now, these button classes can be applied to the  tags, to the  tag,
现在你可以将这些按键类应用到标签 或标签中
as well to the  tags that you use on your web site.
又或应用到你们网页中的标签中
All these can be styled using the button class.
它们都可以通过使用不同的 button 类 来获得不同风格的按钮
So, all of them when you apply the Bootstrap button classes,
当然 当你对这些标签应用 Bootstrap 的按钮类时
will take the form of a button, they all look like a button on the screen.
它们都会长得像一个按钮
But, in particular only button tags can be used inside navs and
不过需要注意的是 只有 button 标签才能被应用到
navbars if you want to include a button in the nav or navbar.
navs 和 navbars 中
Let's take a look at some example buttons and how they are defined in code.
让我们来看一些栗子吧
So, looking at the example that we have on the screen here.
如图所示
You can see that I have defined five different kinds of buttons,
我们在左边定义了五种不同的按钮
the large button that you see there has been styled using button,
那个很大的按钮是用了
button primary, button LG class.
btn, btn-primary btn-lg 来设置的
And, similarly the default, the small success button,
而从左到右的按钮 对应到代码中
the extra small buttons, and even links.
则是从上到下 逐一对应
The two buttons on the right side here
而那两个定义在右边的按钮
they use the button class called button block.
用了一个叫 btn-block 的类
This essentially makes those buttons span
这将会使这些按钮舒展开
the entire payment block within which this button is contained.
并在宽度上占据整个相应板块
So, in this case, the two buttons are spanning an entire column.
在这个例子里 这两个按钮都占满了所有的列
So, they are spanning three columns in that particular row there.
也就是说占满了三列
To summarize, Bootstraps button classes application can be done
综上所述 这些 Bootstrap 中的按钮
by selecting one from each of these four choices here.
其实都是这四种不同设置的组合
So, if you need to apply the button class to any A or Button R, the input element.
当你想要实现一个按钮时
You would specify the class as BTN.
先指定其为 btn
Then followed by one of the color choices that we have there button default,
然后选择颜色
button success, button info and so on.
这里有 7 种选择
Then you can also specify the size of the button.
继而是选择大小
So, you can say button large, button small, button xs.
你可以选择大 中或小
And of course that if you don't specify a size,
当然你也可以不指定大小
the default button size will be used.
那么 Bootstrap 将会帮你选择默认的按钮大小
And you can also make the button
最后就是看要不要设置 btn-block
occupy the entire block by using the btn-block class.
也就是看你想不想让按钮横向充满 当前的整个板块
Bootstrap also allows you to group buttons into button groups.
Bootstrap 还允许你将按钮塞进 同一个按钮组中
So, when you group a set of buttons into button groups,
当你确实这么做了的时候
these buttons are displayed together as a single unit.
这些按钮就会以一个单元的形式显示
So, in the picture what you see here,
如图所示
we have three different kinds of button groups being used.
我们实现了三种不同样式的按钮组
The left two button groups are enclosed inside a button toolbar.
左边两个都被
So, you enclose button groups inside a button toolbar.
封装在了一个 btn-toolbar 中
So, how do we apply the button classes for applying the button group?
那么怎么实现按钮组呢
You use btn-group class, then you can specify the size, also,
直接对一个 div 设置 class="btn-group" 即可
as btn-group -smlgr excess, if you would like to specify.
同时如果你需要的话 你可以通过 btn-group-sm 等来设置按钮组的大小
You can also specify the orientation for the patterns as vertical.
你还可以设置按钮组的排列方向
Normally, the buttons will be done in a horizontal manner if you include them in
通常来说是按钮组中的按钮都是
a button group.
横向排列的
But, you can specify that the button group is button group vertical so
但你也可以设置为纵向排列 也就是 btn-group-vertical
the buttons are going to be laid out stacked one upon the other.
这样那些按钮就会叠在一起
As you see in the example on the right side.
正如图中右边的按钮组所示
So, you have the three buttons in for warning and
我们将 info 按钮 warning 按钮和
danger buttons stacked one on top of the other.
danger 按钮叠在了一起
And the corresponding code for causing this is shown right there in the slide.
而代码的实现也可以在幻灯片上看到
Finally, summarizing, for buttons we have the button class, BTN class,
最后让我们来总结一下
then you have the colors, then you have the sizes that can be used in combination.
首先是 btn 类 然后是颜色 然后是大小
Buttons can be grouped using button toolbar, button group, button group
按钮可以用 btn-toolbar, btn-group, btn-group-vertical btn-group-justified 等来组合在一起
vertical button group justified meaning that the buttons will stretch to occupy
btn-group-justified 代表按钮将会
the entire space that they are allowed to occupy based upon appearance size.
占据所有可能占据的空间
So, if they are included in a column then they stretch to occupy the entire color.
所以如果它们被包含在了一个列里面 它们将会充满整个列
And of course you have the button group with the size being specified large,
当然你还可以通过 lg, sm, xs 来设置
small, and extra small.
btn-group 的大小 【翻译 - Carefree0910】